You there, within that powerful yet weak-willed heart of yours,
find yourself spurred by revolution
You there, heed now the future assured by my unerring nobility
And leave the past behind
Unsuited to such things as ladylike apparel or lipstick
I am envied by god and mortal alike,
for I am a Perfect Knight of Beauty
Pure Amore Love
Let it bloom ever magnificently
A casablanca bursting open like raging magma
Amore, come here,
I shall tell you now the truth
What is “love”?
Love is merely a fantasy for fools.
Yet it is by the whims of love
that we two have been drawn here
Cyalume Change!
Amore, ah!
Avert not your eyes from the flower;
its hue rivaling any shade of crimson
This pristine frenzy is for you
Indeed, it’s for the sake of love
and these dreams that “I” am here